AI Native DevCon is [music] back. The
leading event for engineers and
organizations moving agentic development
into production. Join us on June 1st and
2nd [music] at the Barbican in Central
London. For two full days of workshops,
fascinating talks, and great company.
You'll hear from some amazing speakers
such as Ryan Lepold from OpenAI, Dana
Lawson CTO at Netlify, Justin Cormack
[music] the ex-CTO of Docker, and
Birgitta Buckler from ThoughtWorks.
They'll join speakers [music] from
Anthropic, Nvidia, GitHub, Cisco, Meta,
Adobe, Mozilla, and many [music] more.
This is a practitioner-led community
event and we'd love to have you join us.
Head over to ainativedevcon.io [music]
to grab your ticket. We'll see you
there.